http://www.kate.net/privacy.php

Usage Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS, CONDITIONS, AND PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING THE KATE.NET SITE AND/OR ANY KATE.NET SOFTWARE. BY USING THE KATE.NET WEB SITE AND/OR ANY AND ALL KATE.NET CONTENT, YOU ARE AGREEING TO ALL OF THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND/OR THE PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE EXIT THE KATE.NET SITE NOW.
This policy was last updated on 10/5/17.
Copyright
You acknowledge and agree that any and all information, material, products and services, including data, databases, graphics, text, files, software, interfaces, web pages, product names, company names, trademarks, logos and trade names contained on the Web Site (collectively the “Content”), including the manner in which the Content is presented or appears and all information relating thereto, are the property of Kate.net, its licensors or third parties, as indicated.
Content found on Kate.net is protected under copyright, trademark, proprietary or other intellectual property laws of the United States and other applicable jurisdictions, and any unauthorized use of such Content may violate such laws or this Agreement. Except as expressly provided herein, no license under any copyright, trademark, proprietary or other intellectual property right is granted or implied by granting access to the Content.
While most Content on this site is the intellectual property and original creation of Kate.net, occasionally Content from other parties is used with permission and via license.
Any such Content remains the respective property of its original creator, whether credited as such or not.
Designation of Copyright Agent
While Kate.net never uses unauthorized copyrighted materials from others in any of its works (Kate.net uses only its own, self-created material or material for which a software or image use license is properly and legally obtained), if you believe that your copyright has been infringed, please send a notice to Kate, and your claim will be addressed in a timely manner.
If Kate.net has purchased rights to an image from a stock image service, and that image service has improperly been distributing your image, please let Kate know, and your image will be removed from the work in question, even if Kate.net has appropriately paid money to the stock art service for use of the image, and even if your documented (please provide proof of documentation of your correspondence with the stock art company) dispute with the stock art service has not been rectified.
That is how strongly Kate.net believes in copyrights!
License to Content
You are provided with a limited, personal, non-transferable, non-exclusive license to access, view, read,
download and print (print only such content as is granted permission below to print) the Content, except for Third Party Content and Content that is indicated for sale or that is indicated for distribution pursuant to a separate license agreement (the “Products”). Except as otherwise provided herein or in another written agreement with Kate.net or its Licensors, you may access, view, read, download and print the Content (excluding the Third Party Content and Products) subject to the following conditions:
You may use the Content solely for personal, informational, and internal purposes. Kate.net Wallpapers and Screensavers may be downloaded for personal use only on your home, work, or school computer's desktop, or as your personal iPhone background wallpaper, as applicable.
Kate.net Printables may be downloaded and printed for personal or school use only. You may download a copy of a Kate.net Facebook Cover image to your computer in order that you may then upload it to your personal or nonprofit group or nonprofit school's Facebook page
Kate.net Wallpapers, Facebook covers, and any other graphics may not be used for print purposes, whether in part or in whole.
You may not bundle, sell, license, sublicense, export, transfer, loan, rent, lease, assign, share, outsource, host, publish, distribute, part with possession or make available to any person, the Content, or any part thereof.
You may not copy, edit, modify, adapt, create derivative works, translations, adaptations or arrangements, republish, transmit, merge, reverse engineer, decompile or disassemble the Content, or any part thereof.
You may not use the Content, or any part thereof, or output therefrom, for the direct benefit of any third party, nor shall you charge or receive, either by direct or indirect payment, or by trade of service, compensation, or fees from any third party, for the use of the Content or output therefrom.
You may not alter, remove, or destroy any proprietary markings, or confidentiality legends, or notices placed on, or contained within, the Content; or
You shall not permit, allow or do anything that would infringe or otherwise prejudice the proprietary rights of Kate.net or its licensors or allow any third party to access the Content.
Kate.net reserves the right to revoke the authorization to access, view, read, download and print the Content available on the web site at any time and for any reason, and any such use shall be discontinued immediately without notice from Kate.net. The rights granted to you herein constitute a license and not a transfer of title.
Disclaimer of Warranties
All Content is provided “as is” without any warranties of any kind. You understand and agree that the use of the Content is at your sole risk.
KATE.NET MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS WITH RESPECT TO ANY CONTENT, INCLUDING PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND SOFTWARE AND, TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT ALLOWED BY APPLICABLE LAW, DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES, GUARANTEES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS AND IMPLIED, REGARDING THE CONTENT (INCLUDING PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND SOFTWARE), INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES, GUARANTEES OR CONDITIONS REGARDING ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, COMPLETENESS, CURRENTNESS, AVAILABILITY, EFFECTIVENESS, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY, PRIVACY, TITLE, USEFULNESS, SUITABILITY, QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. FURTHER, KATE.NET MAKES NO REPRESENTATION, WARRANTY OR GUARANTEE THAT THE CONTENT (INCLUDING PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND SOFTWARE) WILL BE SATISFACTORY TO YOUR NEEDS, MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS, OR BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, ACCURATE, SECURE OR FREE FROM ERRORS.
THE INFORMATION ON THE KATE.NET WEB SITE AND CONTENT OF DOWNLOAD FILES FROM THE KATE.NET SITE SHOULD NEVER BE CONSTRUED AS MEDICAL ADVICE. ALWAYS SEEK THE ADVICE OF A PHYSICIAN OR OTHER QUALIFIED HEALTH PROVIDER FOR ANY MEDICAL ADVICE OR FOR THE TREATMENT OF ANY CONDITION.
Limitation of Liability
Kate.net assumes no responsibility to You or any third party for the consequences of any inaccuracy, error or omission on the web site, regardless of cause.
KATE.NET, ITS AFFILIATES, AGENTS, LICENSORS, SUPPLIERS, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS OR EMPLOYEES, SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR DAMAGE OR LOSS OF ANY KIND ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OF, OR THE INABILITY TO USE, THE KATE.NET WEB SITE OR ANY CONTENT (INCLUDING PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND SOFTWARE) PROVIDED THEREIN, OR ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE USE OF ANY WEB SITE LINKED HERETO, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER, SOFTWARE OR OTHER PERSONAL PROPERTY, ANY LOST PROFITS, LOST OPPORTUNITIES, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, EXEMPLARY, AGGRAVATED, ECONOMIC OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGE, EVEN IF KATE.NET IS ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE OR LOSS OR OF A CLAIM BY ANOTHER PARTY.
YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE AND VIEWING OF THE KATE.NET SITE AND ANY AND ALL CONTENT, YOUR USE OF ANY OF THE KATE.NET SOFTWARE OR PRINTABLES, AND/OR FOLLOWING LINKS FROM THE KATE.NET SITE TO OTHER, NON-KATE.NET SITES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK.
THE KATE.NET WEB SITE AND KATE.NET CONTENT ARE HOSTED ON A SERVER PROVIDED BY A THIRD-PARTY HOSTING PROVIDER.
WHILE KATE.NET MAKES EVERY ATTEMPT TO SCAN FILES WITH CURRENT ANTIVIRUS SOFTWARE BEFORE UPLOADING THEM TO THE KATE.NET WEB SITE, KATE.NET MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE ACCURACY OF THE ANTIVIRUS SOFTWARE USED OR THE CONDITION OF THE THIRD PARTY HOSTING PROVIDER'S SERVER, WHETHER TO GUARANTEE SITE AVAILABILITY (UPTIME) OR WHETHER TO GUARANTEE THAT THE THIRD PARTY SERVER IS FREE OF COMPUTER VIRUSES.
Indemnification
You agree to indemnify, defend, and hold Kate.net, its affiliates, agents, licensors, suppliers, or their respective directors or employees, harmless against any and all actions, claims, costs, damages, demands, liabilities, proceedings, expenses or loss of any kind (including legal and other fees and disbursements) sustained, incurred or paid by Kate.net arising out of the access to or use of the Web Site or any Content (including Products and services and Third party Content) contained in or on the Web Site, including any claims arising out of use of the software downloads and printable files.
Third Party Web Sites
Kate.net links to sites not maintained by Kate.net. You are advised that any use of a linked web site and any use of or reliance upon Third Party Content (including products and services) available at such sites is solely at your own risk. In providing links to the other sites, Kate.net is in no way acting as a publisher or disseminator of the material contained on those other sites and does not seek to monitor or control such sites. Kate.net cannot and does not make any representations or warranties with respect to any Third Party Content (including products and services) available through these links and disclaims all liability relating to your use of or reliance upon any Third Party Content (including products and services) available at or through such sites and disclaims any opinions expressed on such web sites. Links to other web sites or references to Third Party Content (including products and services) or publications other than those of Kate.net do not imply the endorsement or approval of such web sites, Third Party Content (including products and services) or publications by Kate.net.
Privacy Philosophy
Kate.net is committed to protecting the privacy of its users, and as such does
not share, exchange, or sell any personally identifiable information such as email addresses,
names, or any other individual-specific information to any third parties.
Furthermore, Kate.net is strongly anti-spam.
What Information is Shared
Kate.net does not currently share any information with any entities; however, may in the future share with third parties (potential advertisers) information relating to general web site usage statistics
(i.e., how many 'hits' the site receives per day, month, etc., what pages are most accessed,
and similar statistics). You can rest assured that no individual personal data is ever disclosed.
What Information is Gathered
Information is gathered by Kate.net in the following ways:
General Usage Data is collected in a Web site usage statistics program.
This shows
how many 'hits' the site receives per day, general domain statistics of visitors (i.e.,
whether visiting domains are .com, .net., etc.; the top visiting domains -- such as
aol.com, etc.), IP addresses of visitors, etc.
Ad Banner Data
Kate.net uses a third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Kate.net website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click on the links provided below.
Google Advertising Network - Text and banner ads from the Google advertising network are also utilized on Kate.net.
Google utilizes cookies in their ads.
Find out more about Google's Privacy Policy for Google Ads.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Other static advertising banners or text and link advertisements are also placed on the Kate.net site; however, those banners or links go directly to the advertisers without going through a third party advertising system, and no personal data is collected by Kate.net via those buttons or banners or links.
Once you have clicked through to an advertiser's site, it is advised that you check their privacy policy for details about how they collect information before you begin using their site.
Links - Kate.net provides relevant links to other web sites, particularly to holiday web sites.
Kate.net is not responsible for the privacy practices and/or the content of such web sites and does not endorse these sites, their services, or their advertisers. The links provided by Kate.net are given for informational purposes only. When visiting such linked sites, you are urged to be an informed surfer and use caution when providing any personal data to these other web sites. If you have any questions, please review the privacy policies on these sites directly.
Kids' Privacy
Although no personally identifiable information is shared,
exchanged, or sold, it is requested that children under 13 not participate in
any of the Kate.net site features without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, whether only to provide an email address or to provide any other elective
information.
Contact Kate.net
If you have any questions regarding the Kate.net Privacy Policy, please feel free
to send an email to Kate.
Copyright © 1994-2020, Kate.net.
All rights reserved.
Terms of Use/Privacy Policy |
Contact |
Kate.net on Facebook
